> > 布莱恩: 现在，这里很酷，如果我详细地说，
&gt;&gt; Brian: Now, what's cool here,
if I go into details,
我要给你看个有趣的把戏
I'm gonna show you just
kinda a fun trick here.
所以我们要把道具带在这里
So we're gonna take in the props here.
我想看看道具里到底是什么
And I wanna see what's actually
coming in from the props.
第一，可能就是使用开发工具，这是最简单的方法。
One, probably just use the dev tools,
cuz that's the easiest way to do it.
但我要给你展示另一种有趣的把戏
But I'm gonna show you
another kind of fun trick
我确实是从 Ryan Florence 学到的
that I did actually learn
from Ryan Florence.
我要说 JSON.stringify(prop，
So, I'm gonna say JSON.stringify(prop,
sNull， 4) >> Brian: 因此，我使用了预先代码和代码。
snull, 4)
&gt;&gt; Brian: So, I used pre and code.
所以，预先格式化和编码，这将成为代码，对吧 ?
So, pre as in preformatted and code and
this is going to be code, right?
我把 JSON 穿成了脑膜炎所以这会顶着道具
And I put JSON stringify, so
this is gonna take props and
就像个漂亮的印张一样
put it into like a nice
pretty printed kinda way.
所以现在我到这里去 /details/ 之类的东西，对吧 ?
So now if I go in here and I go to
/details/ something like that, right?
现在这可能有点难
Now this might be a little hard for
你可以看到但我能看到路由器里的所有东西
you to see but I can see everything
that's coming in from the routers.
路由器实际上提供了相当数量的
The routers actually giving
a pretty substantial amount of
你的信息对吧
information to you, right?
所以，它给了你路径， ID，对吗 ?
So, it's giving you the path,
the ID, right?
请注意该标识在此处与此标识相匹配，
Notice the ID matches this ID up here,
如果我把它换到这里，通知它也会在这里发生变化。
as in if I change it here,
notice it will change down here as well.
URI ，然后是一堆东西的位置，但是端口是哈希，
The URI and then a bunch of stuff location
like but the port is the hash ,the
如果你好奇的话这些都是从历史包里出来的
state that's all coming in from
the history package, if you're curious.
所以如果你这么做
So, if you do this,
在使用 JSON 字符串的代码中预先格式化的代码，如果我在
the pre formatted in code with JSON string
if I would with obviously any object in
这会给你一个漂亮的道具
here, this will give you a nice
pretty printed view of the props.
这也有利于国家的发展，
And this is also useful for
doing with state as well,
如果你想看看国家和道具是如何随着时间的推移而改变的
if you wanna see how state and
props are changing over time.
只是一个小小的调试技术
It's just a nice little
debugging technique to
把东西扔出去
dump something out to the dom.
我也可以走了如果我做了检查
Largely I could also just go,
if I just did Inspect element and
查看此处的 React devtools 。
looked at the React devtools here.
我可以看到同样的信息
I could see the exact same information.
因此，在这里，我的屏幕右边有同样的信息。
So here in Details, that same information
is available on the right of my screen.
你不需要读它只是知道它在那儿
You don't need to read it, but
just know that it's there.
还有，看看有多少组件能到达它们的输出，它相当多。
Also, look how many components reach
their outputs in there, it's quite a lot.
你会看到这个很多的图书馆因为他们要有很多
You'll see this a lot with libraries
because they have to have multiple
不同的层来捕捉它的不同部分那是很典型的
different layers to capture different
parts of it, and that's pretty typical.
我不像这样写代码你把它分成
I don't write code like this
where you separate it out into
各种不同的行为，就像这个位置，地点的提供者，
various different behaviors, like this one
has like a location, location provider,
权利或实施，重点处理程序，重点处理实施。
right or implementation, focus handler,
focus handled implementation.
这里有很多工作要做
There's a lot going on here.
> > 布莱恩: 但你会看到很多图书馆里
&gt;&gt; Brian: But
you'll see that a lot in libraries,
即当此搜索功能变得有用时。
which is when this search
functionality becomes useful.
所以我只能寻找细节我能找到它
So I can just search for
details and I can find it.
> > 布莱恩: 好，有问题吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Good, any questions?
>> 布莱恩: 好 >> 布莱恩: 好的，让我们来吧
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right
&gt;&gt; Brian: So, let's make it so
当你点击这个给我的时候它会带你回到主页上
that when you click this Adopt Me that
it will take you back to the home page,
最重要的是，我想向大家展示如何使用链接。
cuz most people expect that rise, so
I want to show you how to use a link.
这样我们就可以这样离开这里了，我们会在第二个月内解决这个问题。
So we'll leave this like this for
now and we'll fix it in just a second.
我们要回 app.js
We're gonna go back to app.js and
我们要把这个 h1 合并到一个链接里
we're going to wrap this h1 in a link.
所以我要把它连接起来，我要在这里再次使用汽车进口。
So I'm going to put link, and again
I'm going to use the auto import here.
请注意，在此处导入的通知将在第 3 行到达路由器。
Notice that imported that up
here at reach router on line 3.
我就把它关了
And I'll just close that.
我要说链接到 =/
And I'm gonna say Link to =/, and
然后在那个环节里我要把这个给我
then inside of that link,
I'm gonna put this h1.
> > 布莱恩: 其实是这样做的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And actually let's go ahead and
do it this way.
让我们， >> 布莱恩: 消除一切
Let's just,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Get rid of all
我就会把这个放在头里面
the step around link, I'm gonna
actually put this inside of the header.
>> 布莱恩:
&gt;&gt; Brian: Like that.
> > 布莱恩: 所以我在这里做的就是完全删除了 h1 ，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So all I did here is
I deleted the h1 totally, and
然后我就放了标题，然后我就把一个链接放在里面。
then I put header, and
then inside of that I put a link.
这个链接最终会成为一个 A 标签
This link is ultimately
gonna end up being an A tag,
但是使用链接而不是 A 的好东西是到达路由器
but the nice thing about using a link
instead of A is that, reach-router will
自动处理各种不同的路由机制。
handle all of the various different
routing mechanisms for you automatically.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
所以就在 11 到 13 号线上
So just line 11 through 13, there.
> > 布莱恩: 好吗 ? 所以我们来看看这个吧
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay?
So let's go take a look at this, so
现在你可以看到这里如果我点击它
now you can see here
that if I click on it,
它会带我回到主页上对吧
it'll take me back to the homepage, right?
>> 布莱恩: 好的，这主要是我想给你们展示的关于到达路由器的信息。
&gt;&gt; Brian: All right, this is mostly what
I wanted to show you about reach-router.
还有几件事我们可以在这里撒下
There's a couple other things that
we'll kinda sprinkle in here for
其他的当然，但这就像它的关键。
the rest of the course, but
this is like the crux of it.
本身的路由器本身也不必非常复杂
The routers in and of itself
doesn't have to be very complicated
> > 布莱恩: 这里有一个承诺点。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So there's a commit point here.
如果你想达到这个目标你想做的就是
The commit that you wanna roll up to
if you wanna get to this point is,
github btholt 完成 V5，落实。
github btholt complete v5, Commits.
我们是 Add rat router，对吧 ?
We are at Add reach router, right?
所以我们就这样做了
So we just did that one,